

CHATHURIKA RASANGANI Accountant

PERSONAL PROFILE

Result-oriented and organized accounting professional with over 14 years of leadership in financial business areas. Highly trustworthy, discreet, and ethical. I believe learning is driven by attitude, and with dedication, anything can be mastered. My diverse experience has honed my adaptability and excellence in different environments. Seeking new challenges and learning opportunities is my passion.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Name : K.G Chathurika Rasangani

Mobile : +46 73 477 69 75

Email : chathurika.kgc@gmail.com

Address : Rydsvagen 260 B23, Linkoping, Sweden

Personal No: 891002-5728

LinkedIn : www.linkedin.com/in/chathurika-rasangani

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Preparation of Financial Statements
- Budgeting, Forecasting, Costing & Financial Analysis
- Bank Reconciliation
- · Accounts Payable
- Accounts Receivable
- Internal Controls
- · Payroll Management, HR & office administration
- Petty Cash and Cash Management
- VAT Filing & Remittances, Corporate Taxes

SOFTWARE SKILLS

- MS office, Spreadsheets & Emails (Gmail & Outlook)
- FirstBit,1C, Xero, Tally, MYOB, QuickBooks, Oracle
- · Google Docs, Sheets, Slides, forms & google meetings
- "Basecamp" project Management & team communication

SOFT SKILLS

- · Strong written and oral communication
- Adaptability
- Problem-solving skills
- Teamworking ability
- · Positive attitude

LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent Level)
- Sinhala (Native Language)
- Hindi (Intermediate level)

EXPERIENCE

ACCOUNTANT

Key One Realty Group

2022 - 2024

- Maintain accurate and organized financial records to ensure reliable financial reporting.
- · Oversee daily bank transactions and perform regular bank reconciliations.
- Prepare monthly financial and management reports, and client's Statements of Account (SOA).
- Responsible for cash collection, investment, disbursement, and forecasting cash flows.
- Accounts Payable: Ensure bills are paid efficiently and on time
- Accounts Receivable: Issue invoices, track incoming cash flow, report, and follow up on late transactions.
- Handle quarterly VAT filings and payments, and manage related schedules and documentation.

ACCOUNTANT

Bancstac Group

2016 - 2022

Paycorp International (Pvt) Ltd

- Handled general ledger, bookkeeping, and prepared monthly financial statements and management reports.
- Assisted the Group Head of Finance in preparing consolidated accounts, budgeting, cash forecasting, and monthly cost and revenue analysis.
- Oversaw accounts receivables with monthly invoicing and debtor follow-up, and authorized all payment vouchers for accounts payable.
- Company Cash Management (Petty cash, Current accounts, FDs)
- Worked with tax advisers on all company tax matters, and managed the filing of returns.
- Liaised with external auditors to finalize year-end financial reports.
- Managed payroll, EPF, and ETF, and handled company's HR and administrative activities.
- Assisted with the hiring, training, and development of staff, ensuring compliance with company policies and procedures.
- Liaised with banks, secretaries, and other regulatory bodies to ensure compliance and efficient business operations.

ACCOUNTANT

Brescia Grameen (Pvt) Ltd

2015 - 2016

ACCUONTS EXECUTIVE

Melsta logistics (Pvt) Ltd

2011 - 2015

AUDIT TRAINEE

C T Kulathunga Associates

2010 - 2011

EDUCATION

- Bachelor of science (Honors) Business with Financial Management-1st class
- Associate Member in CMA
- Completed Chartered Intermediate Level
- AAT Passed finalist
- Diploma in IT with E-Commerce
- Master of Business Administration (MBA)
 Linköping University, Sweden, Currently Enrolled.